[
  {
    "boxId": 1,
    "name": "English",
    "decks": [
      {
        "deckId": 1,
        "name": "Home",
        "flashcards": [
          {
            "flashcardId": 0,
            "question": "Nescatunga",
            "answer": "American Samoa"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 1,
            "question": "Kohatk",
            "answer": "Vermont"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 2,
            "question": "Forestburg",
            "answer": "Maine"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 3,
            "question": "Mulino",
            "answer": "West Virginia"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 4,
            "question": "Clarksburg",
            "answer": "Tennessee"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 5,
            "question": "Bethpage",
            "answer": "Guam"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 6,
            "question": "Taft",
            "answer": "Wisconsin"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 7,
            "question": "Leming",
            "answer": "Delaware"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 8,
            "question": "Jessie",
            "answer": "Kansas"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 9,
            "question": "Chicopee",
            "answer": "Virginia"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "deckId": 2,
        "name": "Work",
        "flashcards": [
          {
            "flashcardId": 0,
            "question": "Nescatunga",
            "answer": "American Samoa"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 1,
            "question": "Kohatk",
            "answer": "Vermont"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 2,
            "question": "Forestburg",
            "answer": "Maine"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 3,
            "question": "Mulino",
            "answer": "West Virginia"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "deckId": 3,
        "name": "School",
        "flashcards": [
          {
            "flashcardId": 0,
            "question": "Nescatunga",
            "answer": "American Samoa"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 1,
            "question": "Kohatk",
            "answer": "Vermont"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "boxId": 2,
    "name": "Russian",
    "decks": [
      {
        "deckId": 1,
        "name": "Countries",
        "flashcards": [
          {
            "flashcardId": 0,
            "question": "Nescatunga",
            "answer": "American Samoa"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 1,
            "question": "Kohatk",
            "answer": "Vermont"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 2,
            "question": "Forestburg",
            "answer": "Maine"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 3,
            "question": "Mulino",
            "answer": "West Virginia"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 4,
            "question": "Clarksburg",
            "answer": "Tennessee"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 5,
            "question": "Bethpage",
            "answer": "Guam"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 6,
            "question": "Taft",
            "answer": "Wisconsin"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 7,
            "question": "Leming",
            "answer": "Delaware"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 8,
            "question": "Jessie",
            "answer": "Kansas"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 9,
            "question": "Chicopee",
            "answer": "Virginia"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "deckId": 2,
        "name": "At the airport",
        "flashcards": [
          {
            "flashcardId": 0,
            "question": "Nescatunga",
            "answer": "American Samoa"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 1,
            "question": "Kohatk",
            "answer": "Vermont"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 2,
            "question": "Forestburg",
            "answer": "Maine"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 3,
            "question": "Mulino",
            "answer": "West Virginia"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 4,
            "question": "Clarksburg",
            "answer": "Tennessee"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 5,
            "question": "Bethpage",
            "answer": "Guam"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 6,
            "question": "Taft",
            "answer": "Wisconsin"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 7,
            "question": "Leming",
            "answer": "Delaware"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 8,
            "question": "Jessie",
            "answer": "Kansas"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 9,
            "question": "Chicopee",
            "answer": "Virginia"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "deckId": 3,
        "name": "Food",
        "flashcards": [
          {
            "flashcardId": 0,
            "question": "Nescatunga",
            "answer": "American Samoa"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 1,
            "question": "Kohatk",
            "answer": "Vermont"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 2,
            "question": "Forestburg",
            "answer": "Maine"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 3,
            "question": "Mulino",
            "answer": "West Virginia"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 4,
            "question": "Clarksburg",
            "answer": "Tennessee"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 5,
            "question": "Bethpage",
            "answer": "Guam"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 6,
            "question": "Taft",
            "answer": "Wisconsin"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 7,
            "question": "Leming",
            "answer": "Delaware"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 8,
            "question": "Jessie",
            "answer": "Kansas"
          },
          {
            "flashcardId": 9,
            "question": "Chicopee",
            "answer": "Virginia"
          }
        ]
      },
      { "deckId": 4, "name": "Clothes" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "boxId": 3,
    "name": "Turkish",
    "decks": [
      { "deckId": 1, "name": "Home" },
      { "deckId": 2, "name": "Work" },
      { "deckId": 3, "name": "School" },
      { "deckId": 4, "name": "In the restaurant" },
      { "deckId": 5, "name": "Countries" },
      { "deckId": 6, "name": "At the airport" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "boxId": 4,
    "name": "Math",
    "decks": [
      { "deckId": 1, "name": "In the restaurant" },
      { "deckId": 2, "name": "Countries" },
      { "deckId": 3, "name": "At the airport" },
      { "deckId": 4, "name": "Food" },
      { "deckId": 5, "name": "Clothes" }
    ]
  },
  {
    "boxId": 5,
    "name": "Angular",
    "decks": [
      { "deckId": 1, "name": "Home" },
      { "deckId": 2, "name": "Work" },
      { "deckId": 3, "name": "School" },
      { "deckId": 4, "name": "In the restaurant" },
      { "deckId": 5, "name": "Countries" },
      { "deckId": 6, "name": "At the airport" },
      { "deckId": 7, "name": "Food" },
      { "deckId": 8, "name": "Clothes" }
    ]
  }
]
